// an array that stores classes of questions & answers
const STORAGE = 
[
  {
    question:'How much should you set aside in liquid, low-risk savings in case of emergencies?',
    
    answers:['One to three months of expenses', 'Three to six months of expenses', 'Six to 12 months of expenses', 'None and depend on credit card'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'Three to six months of expenses',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'Which of the following is a key benefit of a 401(k) plan?',
    
    answers:['You can withdraw money at any time for needs such as the purchase of a new car.', 'The plan allows you to avoid paying taxes on a portion of your compensation.', 'You may be eligible for an employer match, which is essentially getting free money.', 'None of the above'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'You may be eligible for an employer match, which is essentially getting free money.',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'Which of the following is typically the best way to pursue your long-term goals?',
    
    answers:['Investing as conservatively as possible to minimize the chance of loss', 'Investing equal amounts in stocks, bonds, and cash investments', 'Investing 100% of your money in stocks', 'Investing according to your risk tolerance and goals'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'Investing according to your risk tolerance and goals',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'In debt speak, what does APR stand for?',
    
    answers:['Actual percentage rate', 'Annual personal rate', 'Annual percentage rate', 'Actual personal return'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'Annual percentage rate',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'What is/are the benefit(s) of a Roth IRA?',
    
    answers:['A Roth IRA can provide tax-free income in retirement.', 'Investors can take a tax deduction for their Roth IRA contributions.', 'Investors can make tax-free withdrawals after a five-year holding period for any reason.', 'All of the above'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'A Roth IRA can provide tax-free income in retirement.',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'What is considered a good credit score?',
    
    answers:['85 or above', '500 or above', '600 or above', '700 or above'],
    
    correctAnswer: '700 or above',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'Which is considered a good tip for getting and maintaining a good credit score?',
    
    answers:['Pay all your bills on time.', 'Apply for more credit that you need.', 'Use all of the credit that is available to you.', 'Never order your credit report to dispute errors you find.'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'Pay all your bills on time.',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'What is the benefit of diversification in your portfolio?',
    
    answers:['it decreases risk', 'it eliminates risk', 'it increases risk', 'it makes the portfolio cheaper'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'it decreases risk',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'Which is the safest type of investment?',
    
    answers:['Stock mutual funds', 'Real estate', 'Artwork', 'US government t-bills'],
    
    correctAnswer: 'US government t-bills',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  },
  {
    question:'What dollar amount of the money in a bank or credit union account is protected by the FDIC?',
    
    answers:['Entire amount is protected', 'No amount is protected', '100,000', '250,000'],
    
    correctAnswer: '250,000',
    resultPic:'',
    resultPicAlt: ''
  }, 
]

